Today is a lot of photoshoot and I'm not alone today I have someone with me
Hi, it's Selina.
This is Selina.
And we're going to do some partner outfits today like paradise pants, LeoEx bodies we're already wearing.
We have some other stuff planned.
Let's see how it goes because it's really, really warm again.
I used to say that you can dance the pain away
But the feeling's gone to stay
Your dreams fell out and you're planning to appear
Next set, body suits again
Long sleeve and short sleeve, same colour
with a lot of lorries and trucks around
and it's fine
We're melting
We're melting and we're used to getting stared at when doing pictures outside
I never said I would
Cause my home is my home
Always wise, never slow
Last outfit, I guess it's the last outfit because we're sweating already. Sweating.
Pouring out on the hemlines and the arms. And I tried, I never wore like an orange latex so I
tried to combine with my orange shoes but I think they're too bright but it's okay for the pictures.
Thank you.
Okay, that's it. We're done. I have to take a shower and go home.
I hope you had fun. I did. And I hope the pictures are going to be good.
Because we suffered for them. Okay, see you around. Bye.
By the way, if you want to know more about Selina, check out her channels. I'll link them below. Bye!